Inventory of the American National Red Cross records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Commission for Italy, 1917-1921
  - Correspondence, 1918-1919
    - Department of Civil Affairs, Pisa Contract, 1918-1919 (Reel 140)
      Box/Folder 99: 14-19
  - Reports, 1918-1919
    - Special delegate at Pisa on the works relating to the village, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 100: 1-3
    - Conferences between various persons, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 100: 4-6
    - Transportation Department, 1918
      Box/Folder 100: 7
  - Legal documents relating to the contract for the construction of the village, and preliminary drafts, 1918
    Box/Folder 100: 8
  - Legal documents relating to the contract for the construction of the village, and preliminary drafts, 1918 (Reel 141)
    Box/Folder 100: 9-14
  - Correspondence of the ARC with the Direction of Works (Civil Engineers Corps of Pisa) and with Commissioner Guglielminetti and other functionaries of the Ministry of Public Works, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 101: 1-4
  - Correspondence of the ARC with the Direction of Works (Civil Engineers Corps of Pisa) and with Commissioner Guglielminetti and other functionaries of the Ministry of Public Works, 1918-1919 (Reel 142)
    Box/Folder 101: 5-12
  - Reports of the Direction of Works on the progress of the work on the village, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 101: 13-14. Includes charts
  - Reports of the Direction of Works on the progress of the work on the village, 1918-1919 (Reel 143)
    Box/Folder 101: 15. Includes charts
  - Reports of the Direction of Works on the progress of the work on the village, 1918-1919. Includes charts
    Box/Folder 102: 1-2
  - Daily reports of the Direction of the Works on the number of men employed and the materials delivered at the yard, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 102: 3-5
  - Reports of the Director of Works on the work completed from September 27, 1918, onwards
    Box/Folder 102: 6-7
  - Documents of accounting, progress statements, and payment certificates issued by the Direction of Works, 1918
    Box/Folder 102: 8-13
  - Documents of accounting, progress statements, and payment certificates issued by the Direction of Works, 1918 (Reel 144)
    Box/Folder 102: 14-15
  - Minutes of the inventory of the works and documents relating to the requisition of the village by the military authorities, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 103: 1-4
  - Documents relating to the project for a sewage system for the village, 1918
    Box/Folder 103: 5-8
  - Documents relating to the project for extra toilets and electric illumination for the village, 1918
    Box/Folder 103: 9-13
  - Personnel, 1920
    Box/Folder 103: 14
  - Pisa district, correspondence, including plans for American City at Pisa, 1918-1919 (Reel 145)
    Box/Folder 103: 15
  - Venetian village at Pisa, plans and documents, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 103: 16-18
  - Venetian village at Pisa, plans and documents, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 104: 1-4
  - List of the files of correspondence and documents concerning the construction of the village, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 104: 5
  - Minutes, reports, drafts relating to the project, 1918
    Box/Folder 104: 6-7
  - Documents relating to the construction of a church for the village, 1918 (Reel 146)
    Box/Folder 104: 8-9
  - Kitchen equipment, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 104: 10-13
  - Department of Civil Affairs, documents concerning the construction, 1918
    Box/Folder 104: 14-15
  - Reports on the work for the village Proughi at Pisa, 1918
    Box/Folder 104: 16-17
  - Publicity (news stories to Washington), 1917-1918
    - Aquila
      Box/Folder 105: 1
    - Avellino
      Box/Folder 105: 2
    - Bari (Puglia)
    - Bologna
      Box/Folder 105: 3
    - Capri
      Box/Folder 105: 4
    - Canicattini Bagni, Syracuse
      Box/Folder 105: 5
    - Chioggia (Venice)
      Box/Folder 105: 6
    - Conegliano
      Box/Folder 105: 7
    - Florence
      Box/Folder 105: 8
    - Fourth of July festivities (Reel 147)
      Box/Folder 105: 9
    - Genoa
      Box/Folder 105: 10
    - Italian front
      Box/Folder 105: 11-13
    - Italian Naval School Ship Caracciolo
      Box/Folder 105: 14
    - Italian ports
      Box/Folder 105: 15
    - Leghorn
      Box/Folder 105: 16
    - Lucca
      Box/Folder 105: 17
    - Luino
      Box/Folder 105: 18
    - Messina
      Box/Folder 105: 19
    - Milan
      Box/Folder 105: 20-21
    - Naples
      Box/Folder 105: 22-23
    - Oderzo (war zone)
      Box/Folder 105: 24
    - Padua
      Box/Folder 105: 25
    - Palermo
      Box/Folder 105: 26-27
    - Pavia
      Box/Folder 105: 28
    - Pesaro
      Box/Folder 105: 29
    - Pisa
      Box/Folder 105: 30
    - Reggio Calabria
      Box/Folder 105: 31
    - Rimini (Reel 148)
      Box/Folder 105: 32
    - Riofreddo
      Box/Folder 105: 33
    - Rome
      Box/Folder 106: 1-4
    - Sardinia
      Box/Folder 106: 5
    - Sicily
      Box/Folder 106: 6
    - Taormina
      Box/Folder 106: 7
    - Trieste
      Box/Folder 106: 8
    - Turin
      Box/Folder 106: 9
    - Tuscany
      Box/Folder 106: 10
    - Umbria
      Box/Folder 106: 11
    - Venice
      Box/Folder 106: 12
    - Ventimiglia
      Box/Folder 106: 13
    - Villa San Giovanni, Calabria
      Box/Folder 106: 14
    - Vittoria
      Box/Folder 106: 15
  - Clippings from Italian illustrated newspapers (scrapbook), 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 106: 16
  - Miscellany, unsent letters, a report, and lists of equipment for colonies, 1918
    Box/Folder 106: 17
- Commission for Palestine and Egypt, 1916-1921
  - Accounts, list of invoices, Washington, 1918-1919 (Reel 149)
    Box/Folder 107: 1-2
  - Agricultural work, 1918
    Box/Folder 107: 3
  - American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions, 1918
    Box/Folder 107: 4
  - American Committee for Relief in the Near East, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 107: 5
  - American Consular Service, South Africa, Egypt, Sri Lanka (Colombo), etc., 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 107: 6
  - American Diplomatic Agency, Cairo, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 107: 7
  - American donations, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 107: 8
  - ARC offices, correspondence, reports, 1918-1919
    - Beirut, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 107: 9-10
    - Damascus, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 107: 11
    - London, 1918
      Box/Folder 107: 12
    - Paris, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 107: 13
  - Appreciation, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 107: 14
  - Armenian Benevolent Union, 1919
    Box/Folder 107: 15
  - Armenian Monastery, Bishop Kud, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 107: 16
  - Armenian refugee camp in Port Said, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 107: 17-18
  - Board for Foreign Missions of the Methodist Episcopal Church, New York, 1918
    Box/Folder 107: 19
  - British Red Cross, 1918
    Box/Folder 107: 20
  - Bucharlea, work for refugee hostels, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 107: 21
  - Budget, 1919
    Box/Folder 107: 22
  - Buildings occupied by the ARC, Jerusalem, December 14, 1918
    Box/Folder 107: 23
  - Cairo Office, 1918-1919
    - Correspondence, 1918-1919 (Reel 150)
      Box/Folder 107: 24-27
    - Finance, 1918
      Box/Folder 107: 28
    - Miscellaneous, Commission matters, 1918
      Box/Folder 107: 29
    - Supplies, 1918
      Box/Folder 107: 30
  - "The Captain's Book Presented to Captain John McKellar by Members of the ARC to Palestine in Memory of Their Pleasant Voyage from New York to Colombo March 13-May 22, 1918," typescript
    Box/Folder 108: 1
  - Christian and Missionary Alliance, New York, 1918
    Box/Folder 108: 2
  - Correspondence, general, 1918
    Box/Folder 108: 3
  - Commissioners, general, 1918
    Box/Folder 108: 4
  - Daily News Letter, 1918
    Box/Folder 108: 5
  - Department of Accounts, ARC, National headquarters, Washington, D.C., 1918
    Box/Folder 108: 6
  - Diagram book, Department of Foreign Relief, Jerusalem, 1918
    Box/Folder 108: 7-8
  - Executive Council, correspondence, reports, 1918-1919 (Reel 151)
    Box/Folder 108: 9-10
  - Finances, 1918-1919
  - Budget, 1919
    Box/Folder 108: 11-12
  - General statements sent to Washington, 1918
    Box/Folder 108: 13-14
  - Colonel John H. Finley, correspondence, reports, 1918- 1920
    Box/Folder 108: 15-17
  - French High Commission to Palestine, 1918
    Box/Folder 108: 18
  - Colonel Cathcart Garner, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 108: 19
  - Gaza district, relief work, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 108: 20
  - General headquarters, Cairo, 1918
    Box/Folder 108: 21
  - German Educational Institutions Board, 1918
    Box/Folder 108: 22-23
  - Hospitals at Haifa, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 108: 24
  - Lieutenant Graham C. Hunter, reports on relief work at Bir Zeit, 1918 (Reel 152)
    Box/Folder 109: 1-2
  - Major Henry S. Huntington, Jr., Deputy Commissioner, correspondence, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 109: 3
  - Industrial Department, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 109: 4
  - Instructions for accounting, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 109: 5-6
  - Intelligence reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 109: 7-8
  - International Commission for the Preservation of Jerusalem, 1918
    Box/Folder 109: 9
  - Mousa Kazim Pasha El Husseiny, Mayor of Jerusalem, correspondence, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 109: 10
  - Liquidation, reports, 1919
    Box/Folder 109: 11
  - Local Resources Board, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 109: 12-13
  - Mejdel, relief hospital, 1918
    Box/Folder 109: 14
  - Military orders, 1918-1919
    - General, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 109: 15-17
    - Special, 1918
      Box/Folder 109: 18
  - Minutes of meetings, 1918-1919
    - ARC Commission to Palestine, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 109: 19-22
    - Heads of Departments, 1918 (Reel 153)
      Box/Folder 109: 23-26
    - Heads of Departments, 1918
      Box/Folder 110: 1
    - Joint Advisory Committee for Relief, 1918
      Box/Folder 110: 2
    - Red Cross Council, 1918
      Box/Folder 110: 3
  - Chief Administrator, Major-General Sir A.V. Money, correspondence, 1919
    Box/Folder 110: 4
  - Grand Mufti and Kadi of Jerusalem, address to Commissioner Colonel Finley, 31 July 1918
    Box/Folder 110: 5
  - Mount Zion Orphanage, 1919
    Box/Folder 110: 6-9
  - Nursing Bureau, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 110: 10
  - Occupied Enemy Territory Administration, correspondence, reports, Jerusalem, 1918-1919
    - General, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 110: 11-12
    - Economic Section, 1918
      Box/Folder 110: 13
    - Military Governor's Office, 1918
      Box/Folder 110: 14-15
    - Colonel R.O. Sibley, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 110: 16
    - Colonel J.F. Scrimgeour, 1918
      Box/Folder 110: 17
    - Relief Officer and Refugee Controller for Military Governor Risdon Bennett, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 110: 18
    - Captain W.L. Mason, 1918 (Reel 154)
      Box/Folder 110: 19
    - Local industries, reports, 1918
      Box/Folder 110: 20
    - Orphanages, 1919
      Box/Folder 110: 21
  - Paid bills, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 110: 22
  - Paris Office--Adjustments of account, 1919
    Box/Folder 110: 23
  - Personnel, 1917-1919
    - Americans in British service assigned to ARC
      Box/Folder 110: 24
    - Commission to Palestine, 1918-1919
    - Uniform and insignia, 1917-1919
      Box/Folder 110: 25
    - Status of ARC personnel, 1919
      Box/Folder 110: 26
    - Membership, 1919
      Box/Folder 110: 27
    - Balances of personnel, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 111: 1
    - Lists, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 111: 2-3
    - Contracts, 1919
      Box/Folder 111: 4
  - Port Said--Armenian refugee camp, statements, 1918
    Box/Folder 111: 5-6
  - Purchase--Custody and issue of supplies, 1919
    Box/Folder 111: 7
  - Quartermaster, 1918-1919
    - General, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 111: 8
    - Acknowledgment held for arrival of materials, 1918
      Box/Folder 111: 9
    - Finances, 1918
      Box/Folder 111: 10
  - Ramley detachment, reports, 1918 (Reel 155)
    Box/Folder 111: 11-12
  - Rations, summer scale, 1918
    Box/Folder 111: 13
  - Red Crescent Mission, 1918
    Box/Folder 111: 14
  - Major Edward B. Reed, correspondence, reports, 1919
    Box/Folder 111: 15
  - Refugee camps, 1918
    Box/Folder 111: 16-18
  - Refugee administration, 1919
    Box/Folder 111: 19
  - Relief Committee, 1918-1919
    - General correspondence, reports, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 111: 20-23
    - Relief organizations, 1918
      Box/Folder 111: 24
    - Director of Department of Foreign Relief George Hill, 1918
      Box/Folder 111: 25
    - Relief plans, 1918
      Box/Folder 111: 26
    - American Committee for Armenian and Syrian Relief, 1918
      Box/Folder 111: 27
    - American Committee for Armenian and Syrian Relief, 1918
      Box/Folder 112: 1
    - Subvention to Nazareth Hospital, 1919
      Box/Folder 112: 2
    - Hostels, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 112: 3
    - Syrian and Palestinian Relief Fund, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 112: 4
    - Syrian and Palestinian Relief Fund, 1918-1919 (Reel 156)
      Box/Folder 112: 5-8
    - Director General of Military Relief Jones H. Jesse, 1918
      Box/Folder 112: 9
    - Repatriation and Relief Bureau, 1919
      Box/Folder 112: 10
    - Relief work at salt, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 112: 11-12
    - "A Complete Inventory of Equipment, Supplies, etc. Sold to the American Committee for Relief in the Near East by the ARC Commission to Palestine and the Near East thru the Salvage Board," Jerusalem, 1919
      Box/Folder 112: 13
    - Joint Distribution Committee, New York, 1918
      Box/Folder 112: 14
    - Permanent poor relief, 1918
      Box/Folder 112: 15
  - Russian compound and hospital, 1919
    Box/Folder 112: 16
  - Captain Frederic Remington, correspondence, 1919
    Box/Folder 112: 17
  - Transportation Department, correspondence, 1919
    Box/Folder 112: 18
  - Record of American shipment, 1919
    Box/Folder 112: 19
  - Manager of Insular and Foreign Division, ARC, Washington, Otis H. Cutler, correspondence, 1918
    Box/Folder 112: 20
  - Salvage Board, 1919
    - Minutes of meetings, 1919
      Box/Folder 112: 21-22
    - Inventory, 1919
      Box/Folder 112: 23
    - Disposition of ARC equipment and Salvage Board matters, reports, 1919
      Box/Folder 112: 24
  - Education in the district of Jerusalem, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 112: 25
  - Schools in Bethlehem, accounts, 1913-1918
    Box/Folder 112: 26
  - Seed potatoes supply, 1918 (Reel 157)
    Box/Folder 113: 1
  - Statistics--General, 1918
    Box/Folder 113: 2
  - Classification of accounts, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 113: 3
  - Journal entries, December 1919
    Box/Folder 113: 4
  - Supplies--South Africa, 1918
    Box/Folder 113: 5-6
  - Syrian orphanages, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 113: 7-8
  - Syrian Protestant college at Beirut, 1918-1921
    Box/Folder 113: 9
  - Security Department, telegraph messages, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 113: 10-11
  - Captain John Ward, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 113: 12
  - Remittances to industrials in Palestine, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 113: 13
  - Syria and Palestine Relief Fund, 1917-1918
    - Correspondence, 1917-1918
      Box/Folder 113: 14-15
    - Minutes of meetings, 1918
      Box/Folder 113: 16
    - Tiberias Office, correspondence, 1918
      Box/Folder 113: 17
  - Major Trowbridge, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 113: 18
  - Military Governor Tul Karem, 1919
    Box/Folder 113: 19
  - Reports, 1916-1921
    - General, 1917-1919
      Box/Folder 113: 20-25
    - General, 1917-1919 (Reel 158)
      Box/Folder 113: 21
    - Commission Investigating the Epidemic of Anterior Poliomyelitis in Johannesburg, April 25, 1918
      Box/Folder 113: 26
    - Financial, 1916-1921
      Box/Folder 113: 27
    - Financial, 1916-1921
      Box/Folder 114: 1-7
  - Correspondence, 1918-1919
    - Alleppo, 1918-1919 (Reel 159)
      Box/Folder 114: 8
    - Beirut, 1918
      Box/Folder 114: 9
    - Cairo, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 114: 10
    - Damascus, 1918
      Box/Folder 114: 11
    - Cables from Washington and Paris to Cairo and Jerusalem, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 114: 12-13
    - Port Said, 1918
      Box/Folder 114: 14
    - American Diplomatic Agent and Consul-General Gary Hampson, Cairo, 1918
      Box/Folder 114: 15-17
    - Cables sent from Cairo and Jerusalem to Washington, D.C., 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 114: 18-20
    - Commissioner Edith L. Brooks, 1919
      Box/Folder 114: 21
    - Cables received from Washington, D.C., 1918
      Box/Folder 114: 22
    - Cables from Paris, 1919 (Reel 160)
      Box/Folder 115: 1
    - Copies of cablegrams from Washington, D.C., financial matters, 1919
      Box/Folder 115: 2-3
    - Cables sent to the Secretary of State, Washington, D.C., 1919
      Box/Folder 115: 4
    - War Council, Cornelius N. Bliss, Washington, D.C., 1918
      Box/Folder 115: 5
    - Chairman of War Council Henry P. Davison, Washington, D.C., 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 115: 6-7
  - Colonel John E. Ward, Cairo, 1918
    Box/Folder 115: 8-9
  - Zionism and religious Judaism, 1918
    Box/Folder 115: 10
  - Maps of Palestine, 1917
    Box/Folder 115: 11-12
- Commission for Poland, 1918-1922
  - Appreciation, 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 115: 13-15
  - American Relief Administration, correspondence, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 115: 16
  - Bialystok, reports, 1919, 1921
    Box/Folder 115: 17
  - The Red Cross Bulletin, no. 1, Warsaw, September 15, 1919
    Box/Folder 115: 18
  - Child health, 1920-1922
    - Reports, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 115: 19-20
    - Reports, 1920-1922 (Reel 161)
      Box/Folder 115: 21-22
    - Instructions, 1921-1922
      Box/Folder 115: 23-24
    - Map of child health stations, 1921
      Box/Folder 115: 25
  - Civilian relief, reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 116: 1-2
  - Contracts, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 116: 3
  - General Headquarters, ARC, outline of activities, 1920
    Box/Folder 116: 4
  - Educational Unit, 1921-922
    Box/Folder 116: 5
  - Jews, Alleged discrimination against, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 116: 6
  - Home Service, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 116: 7-8
  - Inventory of supplies, 1919
    Box/Folder 116: 9
  - Liquidation, 1922 (Reel 162)
    Box/Folder 116: 10
  - Paderewski shipment, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 116: 11
  - Polish National Committee and original Polish program, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 116: 12
  - Polish Red Cross, 1921
    Box/Folder 116: 13-14
  - Polish Relief Expedition, 1920
    Box/Folder 116: 15
  - Correspondence, reports, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 116: 16-20
  - Reports by ARC Secretary and Controller Major J.V. Malcolm, 1919
    Box/Folder 116: 21-22
  - Polish Government, 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 117: 1-2
  - Medical work, 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 117: 3-4
  - Medical work, 1919-1922 (Reel 163)
    Box/Folder 117: 5-6
  - "Report on Health Condition in Poland" by Colonel F.F. Longley and Colonel H.A. Shaw, 1921
    Box/Folder 117: 7
  - Miscellany, correspondence, 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 117: 8-9
  - Military relief, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 117: 10-11
  - Ministry of Public Health, 1922
    Box/Folder 117: 12
  - "Child Welfare", report on tour of inspection in Poland and Vienna by Dr. W.O. Pitt, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 117: 13
  - Ministry of War, 1921
    Box/Folder 117: 14
  - Warsaw Office, cables, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 117: 15-17
  - Personnel, reports, 1920
    Box/Folder 117: 18
  - Miscellany, correspondence, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 117: 19
  - Program, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 117: 20-23
  - Publicity, 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 117: 24-25
  - Publicity, 1919-1922 (Reel 164)
    Box/Folder 118: 1-3
  - Refugee work report, 1919
    Box/Folder 118: 4
  - Reports, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 118: 5-15
  - Reports, 1919-1920 (Reel 165)
    Box/Folder 118: 16-20
  - Reports, 1922
    Box/Folder 119: 1-2
  - General report by Walter C. Bailey, 1919
    Box/Folder 119: 3
  - General report by Department of the East with recommendations, May 10, 1919
    Box/Folder 119: 4
  - Quarterly report of ARC throughout Europe, 1920
    Box/Folder 119: 5-6
  - Reports for Chief of Staff Dr. A.J. Chesley, ARC, 1919
    Box/Folder 119: 7-8
  - Reports for Chief of Staff Dr. A.J. Chesley, ARC, 1919 (Reel 166)
    Box/Folder 119: 9
  - Prisoners and refugees of war, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 119: 10-12
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 119: 13-18
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922 (Reel 167)
    Box/Folder 119: 19
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 120: 1-7
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922 (Reel 168)
    Box/Folder 120: 8- 13
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922 (Reel 168 A)
    Box/Folder 120: 14 - 121: 7
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922 (Reel 169)
    Box/Folder 121: 8-14
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922 (Reel 170)
    Box/Folder 121: 15 - 122: 4
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922 (Reel 171)
    Box/Folder 122: 5-10
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922 (Reel 172)
    Box/Folder 122: 11 - 123: 6
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922 (Reel 173)
    Box/Folder 123: 7-11
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922 (Reel 174)
    Box/Folder 123: 12 - 124: 9
  - Regular monthly and special reports for 1919-1922 (Reel 175)
    Box/Folder 124: 10 - end of box
  - Northern district reports, 1920
    Box/Folder 125: 1-2
  - Northern district reports, 1920 (Reel 176)
    Box/Folder 125: 3-12
  - Northern district reports, 1920 (Reel 177)
    Box/Folder 125: 13-16
  - Report on first aid and canteen cars, 1920
    Box/Folder 125: 17-18
  - General report of Walter C. Bailey, 1919
    Box/Folder 125: 19
  - Daily News Bulletin, ARC, Bureau of Publicity, 1920
    Box/Folder 125: 20
  - Photo captions for still pictures, 1920
    Box/Folder 126: 1-2
  - Anti-typhus campaign, 1920
    Box/Folder 126: 3-5
  - Medical reports, 1919-1920 (Reel 178)
    Box/Folder 126: 6-8
  - Bureau of Personnel, reports, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 126: 9
  - Southern district headquarters, Department of Administration, reports of Chief, 1920
    Box/Folder 126: 10-11
  - Documents received from Dr. A.J. Chesley, May 1943
    Box/Folder 126: 12-14
  - Ukrainian prisoners, 1920
    Box/Folder 126: 15
  - Ukrainian relief, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 126: 16-20
  - Special reports for August, 1919 (Reel 179)
    Box/Folder 126: 21
  - Publicity Department, stories, 1920
    Box/Folder 126: 22-23
  - Publicity Department, stories, 1920
    Box/Folder 127: 1-3
  - YMCA, International Committee, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 127: 4
- Balkan States-South Eastern Base, Constantinople Unit, 1917-1923
  - Russian Embassy, minutes of meetings of liaison officers, 20 meetings, 13-30 December 1920 through 4-29 January 1921
    Box/Folder 127: 5
  - Monthly Bulletin, nos. 1-5, November 1921 through March 1922
    Box/Folder 127: 6
  - Appeals, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 127: 7-9
  - Letters of appreciation, 1920-1921 (Reel 180)
    Box/Folder 127: 10
  - American Committee for Relief in the Near East, 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 127: 11-12
  - "Disaster Relief Committee Report", by Foster Stearns, November 15, 1920-July 31, 1921
    Box/Folder 127: 13
  - Correspondence, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 127: 14-15
  - Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Reel 181)
    Box/Folder 127: 16-18
  - Conference minutes, 1920
    Box/Folder 127: 19
  - Child welfare, 1921
    Box/Folder 127: 20
  - Program, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 127: 21-22
  - Personnel, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 128: 1
  - Liquidation, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 128: 2-3
  - Finances, 1920-1922 (Reel 182)
    Box/Folder 128: 4-6
  - Proti Island refugee camp, 1920
    Box/Folder 128: 7
  - Lemnos report, June 30, 1921
    Box/Folder 128: 8
  - Publicity, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 128: 9
  - Reports, 1920
    Box/Folder 128: 10-16
  - Reports, 1920 (Reel 183)
    Box/Folder 128: 17-19
  - Reports, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 129: 1-4
  - Reports, 1921-1922 (Reel 184)
    Box/Folder 129: 5-9
  - Prisoners and refugees of war, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 129: 10-12